You@It should be fixed now, right?
你@應該可以了吧
You@Alright, we've got water now.
你@好了有水了
Shirley@Not bad at all.
謝閔@不簡單啊
Shirley@A rich heir actually fixing the bathroom with his own hands.
謝閔@堂堂富二代竟然親手修浴室
You@I'm sorry about that.
你@對不起啦
You@For making you all put up with this broken bathroom for so long.
你@害妳們忍受這壞掉的浴室那麼久
Shirley@At least you have a conscience.
謝閔@算你還有良心
Shirley@Otherwise...
謝閔@要不然... ...
You@Otherwise what?
你@要不然什麼
Shirley@Otherwise, I might have started looking for a new place to live.
謝閔@要不然我就先找新住所囉
You@The company's a bit tight on money lately.
你@最近公司有點窘迫
You@When things get better,
你@等我好一點
You@I'll definitely buy you all a dryer to make up for it.
你@一定買一台烘乾機賠妳們啦
Shirley@Alright, alright.
謝閔@好啦
Shirley@I know you've been working hard lately.
謝閔@知道你最近很辛苦
Shirley@Here,
謝閔@來
Shirley@Let me wipe off your sweat.
謝閔@幫你擦擦汗
You@Thank you.
你@謝謝妳
Shirley@Since you fixed the bathroom for us,
謝閔@看在你幫我們修好浴室的份上
Shirley@I'll make you a cup of coffee.
謝閔@我幫你泡杯咖啡
You@Sure, that'd be great.
你@好啊
You@I'll go change my clothes.
你@那我去換個衣服
You@Give me a moment.
你@等我一下
Shirley@Okay.
謝閔@好
Shirley@Your coffee, no sugar.
謝閔@你的咖啡不加糖
You@Thank you.
你@謝謝妳啊
Shirley@What's wrong?
謝閔@怎麼啦
Shirley@Are you still thinking about work?
謝閔@你還在想工作的事情啊
You@Yeah,
你@對啊
You@All the waiters at the bar have quit recently.
你@最近酒吧裡的服務生都離職了
You@If we can't find new staff soon, we might have to close down.
你@再找不到人真的要關門了耶
Shirley@That sounds tough.
謝閔@辛苦啦
Shirley@I had no idea you were going through so much lately.
謝閔@還真的不知道你最近發生那麼多事情
Shirley@If I'd known, I wouldn't have caused trouble with renting out your room.
謝閔@早知道我應該不要害你房間租不出去
You@Oh, you dare bring that up?
你@妳還敢說哦
You@Even people coming to view the room have decreased recently.
你@最近連來看房的人都變少了
You@It feels like it's getting harder to rent it out.
你@感覺租出去更難了
Shirley@I'm sorry about that.
謝閔@對不起啦
Shirley@How about I try to find some other people to come?
謝閔@還是我找其他人來嘛
You@Of course, that'd be great.
你@當然好啊
You@The more, the better.
你@而且越多越好
You@Speaking of which,
你@說到這個
You@Have you chatted with Regina recently?
你@妳最近有跟蕾江聊天嗎
You@She's been acting a bit strange.
你@她感覺怪怪的耶
Shirley@Strange how?
謝閔@哪裡怪
You@It's been a bit hot lately, right?
你@最近不是有一點熱嗎
You@So I came to check if there were any problems in the dorm.
你@我就來看一下宿舍有什麼問題
You@But I saw her downstairs wearing a large coat and acting all sneaky.
你@結果看到她在樓下穿著一件大衣而且還鬼鬼祟祟的
You@Like she was afraid of me seeing her.
你@好像很怕我看到一樣
Shirley@Oh, yeah.
謝閔@對耶
Shirley@I've seen her going out at night wearing a big coat recently.
謝閔@我最近晚上有看到她穿一件大衣就出門
Shirley@Maybe she's got a boyfriend?
謝閔@可能是交男朋友啦
You@That's possible.
你@有可能喔
You@She seems like the type who'd completely change when she gets a boyfriend.
你@她感覺就是那種交男朋友會變一個人的人
Shirley@Alright, let's not worry about her.
謝閔@好啦不管她了
Shirley@I'm going to livestream tonight to sell some clothes I designed.
謝閔@我晚上要直播賣一些我設計的衣服
Shirley@Want to help me out?
謝閔@你要來幫我嗎
Shirley@I could use an assistant.
謝閔@我剛好缺一個幫手